<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cognotekt.com</title>
    <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cognotekt.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>title.en</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/home/title/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/home/title/</guid>
      <description>Content of the file goes Here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>wwd.en</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/home/wwd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/home/wwd/</guid>
      <description>Content of the file goes Here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>solutions.en</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/home/solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/home/solutions/</guid>
      <description>Content of the file goes Here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>howwework.en</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/home/howwework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/home/howwework/</guid>
      <description>Content of the file goes Here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hwa.en</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/home/hwa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/home/hwa/</guid>
      <description>Content of the file goes Here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jobs.en</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/home/jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/home/jobs/</guid>
      <description>Content of the file goes Here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>blog</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/home/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/home/blog/</guid>
      <description>Content of the file goes Here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backend-Developer for Cloud-based Services</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/job/backenddeveloperbigdata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 12:24:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/job/backenddeveloperbigdata/</guid>
      <description>Cognotekt GmbH is the German market leader in automating and improving repetitive business processes consisting of mental activities. We analyse and reproduce them using mathematics and artificial intelligence. And we’re growing, so we need more colleagues to realise our visions. Offer: Your tasks are the design and development of backends for data-driven services for the optimization and automatisation of business processes. Our components are realized in Go and Python (with a core in C or C++).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entwickler(in) Künstliche Intelligenz</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/job/beraterentwicklerk%C3%BCnstlicheintelligenz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 12:24:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/job/beraterentwicklerk%C3%BCnstlicheintelligenz/</guid>
      <description>Cognotekt GmbH ist eine auf die Automatisierung und Qualitätssteigerung von Geschäftsprozessen spezialisierte Software- und Beratungsfirma. Wir rationalisieren Prozesse, die aus repetitiven, einfachen geistigen Tätigkeiten bestehen, indem wir die Prozesse analysieren und die Schritte, die durch Algorithmen abbildbar sind, automatisieren oder durch den Einsatz von Mathematik qualitativ verbessern. Damit sind wir am deutschen Markt führend. Stellenbeschreibung: Ihre Aufgaben umfassen die Erstellung von KI-Komponenten zur Automatisierung und Qualitätssteigerung von Geschäftsprozessen. Die Komponenten realisieren durchgehend höhere Mathematik als Software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linguist/Analyst Künstliche Intelligenz</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/job/linguistanalystk%C3%BCnstlicheintelligenz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 12:24:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/job/linguistanalystk%C3%BCnstlicheintelligenz/</guid>
      <description>Cognotekt GmbH ist eine auf die Automatisierung und Qualitätssteigerung von Geschäftsprozessen spezialisierte Software- und Beratungsfirma. Wir rationalisieren Prozesse, die aus repetitiven, einfachen geistigen Tätigkeiten bestehen, indem wir die Prozesse analysieren und die Schritte, die durch Algorithmen abbildbar sind, automatisieren oder durch den Einsatz von Mathematik qualitativ verbessern. Damit sind wir am deutschen Markt führend. Stellenbeschreibung: Ihre Aufgabe ist die Systematisierung von Fachanforderungen und die linguistische Analyse von fachsprachlichen Texten als Vorbedingung für die Entwicklung von KI-Systemen in der Wirtschaft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum-Master mit Branchenfokus Gesundheitswesen</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/job/scrum-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 12:24:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/job/scrum-master/</guid>
      <description>Scrum-Master mit Branchenfokus Gesundheitswesen Cognotekt GmbH ist eine auf die Automatisierung und Qualitätssteigerung von Geschäftsprozessen spezialisierte Software- und Beratungsfirma. Wir rationalisieren Prozesse, die aus repetitiven, einfachen geistigen Tätigkeiten bestehen, indem wir die Prozesse analysieren und die Schritte, die durch Algorithmen abbildbar sind, automatisieren oder durch den Einsatz von Mathematik qualitativ verbessern. Damit sind wir am deutschen Markt führend. Stellenbeschreibung: Ihre Aufgabe besteht darin, in der agilen Softwareentwicklung in mehreren Projekten die Anwendung und Optimierung des Scrum-Vorgehensmodells sicherzustellen, insbesondere auch ein Scrum of Scrums zu etablieren.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systemarchitekt Künstliche Intelligenz (KI)</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/job/systemarchitekt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 12:24:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/job/systemarchitekt/</guid>
      <description>Cognotekt GmbH ist eine auf die Automatisierung und Qualitätssteigerung von Geschäftsprozessen spezialisierte Software- und Beratungsfirma. Wir rationalisieren Prozesse, die aus repetitiven, einfachen geistigen Tätigkeiten bestehen, indem wir die Prozesse analysieren und die Schritte, die durch Algorithmen abbildbar sind, automatisieren oder durch den Einsatz von Mathematik qualitativ verbessern. Damit sind wir am deutschen Markt führend. Stellenbeschreibung: Sie konzipieren auf der Grundlage klar strukturierter Anforderungen die Architektur unserer Systeme, die auf der Cloud modular, lose gekoppelt und verteilt sehr komplexe Funktionalität aus dem Bereich der KI abbilden und dadurch ganze Prozessabschnitte unserer Kunden automatisieren.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colleague robot</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/blog/2017/05/20/kollegeroboter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 12:24:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/blog/2017/05/20/kollegeroboter/</guid>
      <description>(&amp;hellip;)
Cologne-based company Cognotekt ñ that automates business processes using artificial intelligence ñ making countless jobs in insurance redundant ñ shows how realistic the risk already is for desk workers. At the moment, the German insurance industry employs tens of thousands of handlers to carry out investigations into whether there is an attempted fraud or whether the insurance might be able to reduce the claim sum. ìIn ten years, no more than 20 percent of these employees will still be neededî, predicts Cognotekt managing director Jobst Landgrebe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every claims handler is replaceable</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/blog/2017/05/20/jederscjadembearbeiter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 12:24:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/blog/2017/05/20/jederscjadembearbeiter/</guid>
      <description>(&amp;hellip;)
The insurance industry is in relentless digital turmoil. Which is almost no difference to other industries. But, it is being hit harder for two reasons: due to the strict regulation of products and companies, there have been market entry barriers, through which technical innovations have long been unable to penetrate the conservative industries. In addition, the linguistic and graphical contents, which insurers deal with, are very complex. As a result, it was more difficult to automate them than in logistics or online trading, where only numbers have to be processed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insurers want to be like Amazon</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/blog/2017/05/20/versichererwollen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 12:24:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/blog/2017/05/20/versichererwollen/</guid>
      <description>(&amp;hellip;)
If Jobst Landgrebe had his way, insurers would have to be much faster. The founder and owner of Cognotekt relies on artificial intelligence as a provider of efficiency. For years, the businessman worked in the insurance industry and recognised that many claims are so similar that they could be automated successfully. He has built a robot for a service provider in the car insurance business, which examines cost estimates or invoices from workshops to see if they are objectionable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supercomputer replaces insurance workers in Japan</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/blog/2017/05/20/supercomputerersetzt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 12:24:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/blog/2017/05/20/supercomputerersetzt/</guid>
      <description>(&amp;hellip;)
Artificial intelligence is also a subject being discussed by German insurers. The management consultancy EY Innovalue has just completed a study about how there is still a major discrepancy between perceived opportunities and the actual willingness to change. Accordingly, 75†percent of companies questioned considered automated claims investigation, automated cover verification after simple claims and automated auditing of reports and invoices to be a relevant topic for the future. Up to now, the discussion of these topics within companies has been controversial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual insurance detectives</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/blog/2017/05/20/virtuelleversicherungsdetektive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 12:24:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/blog/2017/05/20/virtuelleversicherungsdetektive/</guid>
      <description>(&amp;hellip;)
The first suppliers are already tweaking appropriate technology using artificial intelligence. Cognotekt from Cologne has developed software which is based on a learning, stochastic algorithm. Founder Jobst Landgrebe gives an example: a patient wants to draw a benefit from a sick pay insurance policy. The intelligent computer analyses large quantities of data, for example the medical history, and checks how probable it is that the policyholder is actually ill. For unsuspicious cases, it triggers the payment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impressum</title>
      <link>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cognotektgmbh.github.io/en/contact/</guid>
      <description>Legal details Cognotekt GmbH Bonner Str. 209 50968 Cologne
info@cognotekt.com +49221-643065-10
Managing partner Dr. Jobst Landgrebe Tax no.: 219/5807/3005 Commercial registry no.: HRB 71466 District Court of Cologne
Data protection guideline Please note that “Google Analytics” is complemented by “gat._anonymiozelp();” on this website. This ensures that IP addresses can be recorded in an anonymous manner (IP masking). This website uses “Google Analytics”, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>